<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Aesthetic &#8211; CityThreads</title>
	<atom:link href="https://citythreads.netlify.app/categoria-producto/clothing/aesthetic/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://citythreads.netlify.app</link>
	<description>CityThreads is an urban clothes ecommerce that offers trendy and stylish clothing for the city dweller.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:29:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://citythreads.netlify.app/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/CityThreads_Logo-removebg-preview.png</url>
	<title>Aesthetic &#8211; CityThreads</title>
	<link>https://citythreads.netlify.app</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Casual Shoes</title>
		<link>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/casual-shoes/</link>
					<comments>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/casual-shoes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jphuicidev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 17:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://citythreads.netlify.app/?post_type=product#038;p=934</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<blockquote>Step up your game with comfortable and stylish Casual Shoes</blockquote>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our Casual Shoes are designed to offer the perfect combination of comfort and style, with a range of designs that are perfect for any occasion. From classic sneakers to loafers and slip-ons, our shoes are made from high-quality materials and feature sleek and modern designs that are always on-trend. Whether you&#8217;re running errands or going out with friends, our Casual Shoes offer the perfect mix of comfort and style, allowing you to step up your game and feel confident and comfortable all day long. Discover the ultimate in style and comfort with our Casual Shoes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/casual-shoes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Urban Pants</title>
		<link>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/urban-pants/</link>
					<comments>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/urban-pants/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jphuicidev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 17:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://citythreads.netlify.app/?post_type=product#038;p=933</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<blockquote>Urban Pants: Style meets comfort for everyday wear</blockquote>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our Urban Pants are designed to offer both style and comfort, with a versatile range of designs that are perfect for everyday wear. Made from high-quality materials and crafted with attention to detail, our pants feature modern and sophisticated designs that are perfect for the urban lifestyle. From slim-fit to relaxed styles, our pants offer a perfect fit for every body type. Whether you&#8217;re dressing up for a night out or keeping it casual, our Urban Pants are the perfect choice for a stylish and comfortable look that&#8217;s always on-trend. Experience the perfect blend of style and comfort with our Urban Pants.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/urban-pants/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Snow</title>
		<link>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/snow/</link>
					<comments>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/snow/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jphuicidev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 16:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://citythreads.netlify.app/?post_type=product#038;p=931</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<blockquote>Soft, serene, and tranquil, winter's blanket of pure, white snow</blockquote>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our Snow collection captures the tranquility and serenity of winter, offering a range of cozy and comfortable apparel and accessories that are perfect for cold weather. Featuring soft, plush fabrics and a muted color palette, our Snow collection is designed to evoke the feeling of a winter wonderland. From warm and stylish jackets to soft and comfortable accessories like scarves and hats, our Snow collection has everything you need to stay cozy and stylish this winter. Embrace the magic of winter with our Snow collection.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/snow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stylish</title>
		<link>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/stylish/</link>
					<comments>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/stylish/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jphuicidev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 16:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://citythreads.netlify.app/?post_type=product#038;p=930</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<blockquote>Elegance and fashion combined, classic and modern, forever stylish</blockquote>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our Stylish outfit is the perfect blend of classic and modern, offering an elegant and fashionable look that&#8217;s always on-trend. Featuring high-quality fabrics and attention to detail, this outfit exudes sophistication and style. From the sleek lines of the tailored pants to the effortless elegance of the blouse, this outfit is designed to make a statement. Whether you&#8217;re dressing up for a special occasion or simply want to elevate your everyday style, our Stylish outfit is the perfect choice. Make a statement and exude confidence with our Stylish outfit.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/stylish/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cityzen</title>
		<link>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/cityzen/</link>
					<comments>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/cityzen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jphuicidev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 16:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://citythreads.netlify.app/?post_type=product#038;p=928</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<blockquote>Urban style, metropolitan edge, global perspective, Cityzen fashion for all</blockquote>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our Cityzen jackets are designed to embody the spirit of urban living, offering a metropolitan edge with a global perspective. Made from high-quality materials and crafted with attention to detail, our jackets are both stylish and functional. With a range of designs and colors to choose from, our Cityzen jackets are perfect for those who want to make a statement with their outerwear. From lightweight options for warmer weather to cozy and insulated styles for colder climates, our jackets are versatile and practical. Elevate your urban style with our Cityzen jackets.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/cityzen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aesthetic</title>
		<link>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/aesthetic/</link>
					<comments>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/aesthetic/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jphuicidev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 02:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://citythreads.netlify.app/?post_type=product#038;p=925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<blockquote>Beauty in simplicity, minimalistic design, timeless elegance, aesthetic charm</blockquote>
&#160;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our Aesthetic collection celebrates simplicity and timeless elegance, offering a range of minimalist designs that exude an understated charm. Featuring clean lines, muted colors, and classic shapes, our collection is designed for those who appreciate the beauty of simplicity. From sleek and modern accessories to minimalistic apparel, our Aesthetic collection is perfect for those who value clean, uncluttered design. Embrace the beauty of simplicity with our Aesthetic collection.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/aesthetic/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rose Gold</title>
		<link>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/rose-gold/</link>
					<comments>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/rose-gold/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jphuicidev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://citythreads.netlify.app/?post_type=product#038;p=905</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<blockquote>Luxurious, feminine, and elegant, a timeless beauty in rose gold</blockquote>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our Rose Gold collection is the epitome of luxury and femininity. With a soft, pink hue and a touch of shimmer, rose gold is a timeless and elegant choice for any occasion. Our collection includes a range of jewelry, glasses, and accessories, crafted from high-quality materials and featuring intricate details and designs. Whether you&#8217;re looking to add a touch of elegance to your everyday wear or elevate your formal attire, our Rose Gold collection is the perfect choice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://citythreads.netlify.app/producto/rose-gold/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
